(Howard:)So I got the craziest e-mail
this morning.
l don't mean to burst your bubble,
but penile-enlargement pills do not work.
(Howard:)Believe me, I know.
(Howard:)The e-mail I got was from the office
of Stephen Hawking.
- You're kidding.
- Why?
(Howard:)He's coming to the university
to lecture...
(Howard:)...and he's looking for an engineer to
maintain equipment on his wheelchair.
(Leonard:)That's amazing.
You'll be like his pit crew.
(Leonard:)A word of caution, I would not do
your Stephen Hawking impression...
(Leonard:)...in front of him.
(Howard(in Stephen Hawking voice):)You're right.
l suppose
that could be considered offensive.
(Raj:)Oh, boy.
Oh, Sheldon's going to freak out.
(Leonard:)Yeah, he worships Hawking.
l was thinking about bringing him along,
so he can meet the great man.
- That's really nice of you, Howard.
- It's no big deal.
(Leonard:)Boy, a restraining order
from Stephen Hawking.